To Whom It May Concern.

My Name is Anthony J. Manenti -

I am an enthusiastic problem solver, who loves big ideas, and big challenges. I enjoy

collaborative effort. I have a knack for putting ends together in the pursuit of creating

useful tools, and unforgettable user experiences. I have always been a thinker and a

tinkerer. I enjoy the creative process involved in creating truly dynamic, fluid, and

compelling applications.

I have over a decade worth of work experience in Tech. I started from humble

beginnings as a computer repair technician and have worked with managed service

providers in the triangle area. My work has always pushed me, and has been humbling.

There is always something new to learn.

I am a Graduate of UNC - Greensboro's College of Arts and Sciences. I am also a

graduate of The Coding Bootcamp at UNC Chapel Hill's Spring 2018 cohort where I was

exposed to the MERN stack of technologies used in the creation of web based

applications.

I am a coder. I enjoy creating memorable UX/UI elements and the technical process of

creating boilerplate needed to run applications.

Yours truly,

Anthony J. Manenti

Applicant

https://github.com/imaginethat01

ANTHONY J. MANENTI

Professional Resume:

Education:

• University of North Carolina - Greensboro

Bachelors of Arts and Sciences Concentration : English Literature. Publishing. Design.

• The Coding Bootcamp at The University of North Carolina

Intensive course in Full Stack Development

Fluency in MERN Stack and the development of dynamic applications using front and back-end technologies and database query languages.

Work History:

• Imagine That Solutions

2013 - 2018 Primary Account Representive

Assisted local business owners in the creation and implementation of POS and e-commerce solutions. Analytics and digital advertisement. Including complete web builds.

• The ITGuys

2017-2018 Technical Specialist

Responsible as an MSP to a list of clients. And assistant in the installation of business and enterprise class networking assets.

• Intrex Computers INC / Microbarn.com

2013-2015 Lab Technician, Warehousing Agent.

Learned the fundamentals of diagnostics and computer repair, accounting and how to manage large sets of inventory.